<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>INDIRA GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY FOR WOMEN</title>
 <link>http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54</link>
 <description></description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>VC&#039;s Message</title>
 <link>http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54/?q=administration/vcs-message1</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;section field field-name-field-image field-type-image field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54/sites/default/files/styles/medium/public/Prof.NupurPrakash.jpg?itok=jIXo-85z&quot; width=&quot;157&quot; height=&quot;220&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;section field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;rtecenter&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:16px&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:#008000&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice Chancellor&#039;s Message&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;rtejustify&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:14px&quot;&gt;Capability is Gender Neutral! It is always recognized and rewarded sooner or later irrespective of gender. However, the field of science and technology has traditionally witnessed low female participation and the representation of women in engineering industry is around 20% only. There is a huge demand for competent women engineers in our country and therefore Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women has a major role to play in capacity building and imparting high quality technical education to the women of our country. The mandate of this University is to educate women leading towards their enlightenment, employment and empowerment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;rtejustify&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:14px&quot;&gt;The University aims to incubate new ideas, encourage innovation and research work in the discipline of Engineering, Science and Technology.  The University offers a number of B.Tech, B.Arch, M.Tech and Ph.D programmes in the area of engineering and technology. The objective of the University is to promote research among young women engineers and to provide knowledge workers to boost the knowledge economy of our country. I am extremely confident that Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women will continue to scale new heights and serve the society by nurturing budding women engineers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;rtejustify&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:14px&quot;&gt;The students of our University have been placed in many prestigious companies in the last 10 years and continue to excel in higher studies within India and abroad. Our mission is to foster an environment for attaining excellence in professional education and promote active participation of women in the field of Engineering, Science, Architecture and Technology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:14px&quot;&gt;Prof. Nupur Prakash&lt;br /&gt;
Vice Chancellor, IGDTUW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 08:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>shreya</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">377 at http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54</guid>
 <comments>http://172.16.19.10/drupal-7.54/?q=administration/vcs-message1#comments</comments>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
